Rameş Aliyev

My name is Rameş Aliyev (IPA: [xameʃ alijev]), and I'm a former Software Engineer who mostly experienced in Web Technologies. I've worked in various companies as a senior or a lead engineer. For the last couple of years, I returned to academia to improve my theoretical background.



These days, I'm studying Computer Science at Yildiz Technical University as an initial step of my becoming a AI Scientist journey. I mostly interested in Computer Vision and Deep Learning in general.

linkedin. github. scholar. resume. kaggle. twitter. chess. goodreads.

email: ramesaliyev ⊽ gmail ∘ com

publications

2022 Age Estimation from Pediatric Panoramic Dental Images with CNNs and LightGBM

education

```
2019 - 2023 BSc, Computer Science - Yildiz Technical University

2016 - 2018 ASc, Computer Programming - Sakarya University
```

certifications

2021 NVIDIA, Deep Learning Institute Fundamentals of Deep Learning
2020 Coursera, Duke University Data Science Math Skills

work experience

```
2012 - 2023 Undergraduate Research Fellow - Yildiz Technical University

2017 - 2021 Co-Founder & Full Stack Developer - Ecma

2018 - 2020 Senior Full Stack Developer - Omma

2018 - 2018 Senior Frontend Developer - Pisano

2016 - 2017 Lead Full Stack Developer - Emlakjet

2013 - 2015 Senior JavaScript Developer - Turkcell

2013 - 2013 JavaScript Developer - E-Net

2012 - 2013 Frontend Developer - Techpoint Labs

2009 - 2012 Full Stack Developer - Koridor Design Studio
```

teaching / workshops

```
2017 instructor Javascript Fundamentals, Frontend Camp'17 Summer
2016 instructor Full Stack Javascript Development, TV8 Acun Medya
2015 organiser Free For All, JSNinjas
2015 speaker Modern Javascript Architecture, The Frontiers:Mini
```